Previously on desperate housewive.
绝望主妇 前情提要
Dave got caught.
Dave被逮捕了
You change your name and you're living in fair view.
你改了名字 过着平静的小日子
It's not healthy or safe.
可这既不安全 也不健康
Gaby got leverage.
Gaby找到了一个平衡点
I'm getting that bonus after all.
无论如何 我都能得到好处
So, Brad, what sort of bonus are we looking at?
那么 Brad 我们是在指什么样的好处呢?
- Katherine dropped a bomb.  - Mike's moving in here.
Katherine丢了颗炸弹 Mike要搬来住了
- What?
- 什么?
Tom called it quits.
Tom要关门了
If we're gonna sell this place,
既然我们要卖掉这里
- we should probably know exactly how much it's worth.
- 我们也该知道它值多少钱
And Bree got honest...
Bree也说了实话...
- You're paid based on your contribution.
- 你干多少就得多少
You're saying I'm worthless.
你的意识是我是个废物
No, I'm just saying you're worth... less.
没有 我只是说你并不是那么... 能干
Which resulted in some strange behavior.
这也导致了一些奇怪的行为
Everyone who met Orson Hodge,
每一个见到Orson Hodge的人
knew he believed in being polite.
都知道他喜欢彬彬有礼
He greeted his neighbors each day with a sunny...
他每天都一脸阳光地向邻居说...
Good morning.
早上好啊
He opened doors for young women with a gallant...
他为拿着大包小包的女士开车门 说...
Allow me.
请让我来
If he bumped into a stranger on the street...
如果他在街上撞上一个陌生人...
Oh!
哦!
He'd cheerfully say...
他会满脸带笑地说...
I beg your pardon.
请原谅
And if one of his friends was having a hard time,
如果他的朋友有了点麻烦
Orson was the first to say...
Orson总会第一个开口说...
You need some help there?
需要帮忙吗?
Whether his friend wanted his help or not.
无论他的朋友是否想要他的帮助
Orson.
Orson
What are you doing here?
你来这里干什么?
Well, I heard about your going out of business sale,
哦 我听说你不准备干了
and I thought you could use a hand.
我觉得你可能需要点帮助
I'm good. Thanks.
我很好 多谢你的美意
Oh! Wow, this is charming.
哦! 哇塞 这个真可爱
Oh. It's a salt shaker my grandfather gave me.
啊 那个是我祖父送给我的盐瓶
Used to display it on the shelf.
一般都把它放在货架上做摆设
How much you want for it?
这个你卖多少钱?
It's not for sale.
它不是拿来卖的
Everything in that box is stuff I'm taking with me.
那箱子里的东西是我要留着的
Oh. Okay.
哦 那好吧
Just trying to help out.
只是想来帮下忙
I know it's a difficult day.
我知道这日子不好过
And I think I, of all people,
在所有人中 我很明白
understand what it is you're going through.
你现在的处境
Why you "of all people"?
为什么要说"在所有人中"?
Well, I know what it's like
我知道突然没了生计
to have your livelihood suddenly vanish.
是什么样的感觉
Remember, I used to be a dentist.
你要知道 我当过牙医
Oh, right.
哦 是啊
Right.
对
Of course, it's not really the same, is it?
这两件事可不太一样吧?
- What's this?
- 此话怎讲?
My business started going sout because of a bad economy.
我的生意是因为经济不景气才黄的
It got worse when my son
尤其当我的儿子因为自己压根儿
was accused of a crime that he didn't commit.
没做过的事而被起诉后 更是每况愈下
But you lost your license because you went to prison
但是你进监狱 丢了执照
for a crime you did commit.
是因为你确实干了坏事
Why are you being this way?
你为什么要说这种话?
Because what's happening to me is unfair.
因为发生在我身上的事很不公平
- What happened to you was...
- 而你身上发生的事...
Justice?
非常公平?
Yeah. And to compare my situation with yours,
没错 然后在这样的一天里
on a day like this,
将我和你的处境相比
well, I gotta tell you, it's a little insulting.
我得说 这有点伤自尊
Then I apologize.
那我向你道歉
My intention was never to insult you.
我从没想要伤你的自尊
I wanted to support you in your... in your hour of need.
我只是想在... 在你需要之时帮助你
Uh-huh, um... vultures are starting to arrive.
啊哈 嗯... 豺狼来了
I'll leave you to it, then.
那我就不打扰你了
Yes, everyone who met Orson Hodge
没错 凡是见到Orson Hodge的人
knew he believed in being polite.
都觉得他喜欢彬彬有礼
What they didn't know is,
但他们不知道的是
that he also believed
他还喜欢惩罚
in punishing those who weren't.
那些不太礼貌的人
The day after Mike Delfino
在Mike Delfino和Katherine Mayfair
moved in with Katherine Mayfair.
住到一起后的第二天
She thought it would be nice to share her happiness.
她觉得应该和别人分享一下自己的喜悦
So she decided to throw a housewarming party
所以她决定邀请邻里朋友
for her friends and neighbors.
举办一场搬家庆祝派对
But from the moment the first invitation was delivered,
但是从请柬被送出去的那一刻起
her friends began making assumptions
她的朋友们就开始谈论
about those who had been invited...
那些被邀请了的人...
And about those who hadn't.
和那些没被邀请的人
I know it's late, but I do hope
我知道这可能晚了点
- you'll be able to make it.
- 但是我真心希望你们能来
Now does this really mean no gifts,
这个是真的说不要带礼物
or is it like when Gaby says "no gifts",
还是说像Gaby一样 嘴上说不要带礼物
- and she means nocheap gifts?
- 实际意思是说不要带廉价礼物?
You know, Katherine, if you need any help,
Katherine 如果你需要帮忙的话
- I would be happy to make my...
- 我随时都乐意...
Sh.
嘘
Hey, guys, what are we talking about?
嗨 姐妹们 你们聊什么呢?
The federal deficit.
政府赤字
Whoo! That sucker's big!
哇噢! 真他妈的大啊!
Actually, Susan, we were talking about my housewarming party.
Susan 其实我们在谈搬家庆祝派对
Oh, yeah, I'm so excited. You got my r.s.v.p. right?
哦 对 我好兴奋啊 你收到了我的请柬回复吧?
Yes, I'm so glad you're coming, oh, um, by the way,
当然 我真高兴你能来 嗯 问下
- can you bring your blue punch bowl?
- 你能把那个捣沙拉用的蓝色碗拿来吗?
Absolutely. Anything else you need?
没问题 你还需要别的什么吗?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, what's happening here?
喂 喂 喂 这是怎么了?
Why isn't hair being pulled?
你们俩不是应该打起来吗?
Why would we do that?
为什么要那么做?
Um... Let's see. She's shacking up with your ex?
嗯 我想想啊 因为她和你的前老公搞上了?
Something which when I do it, I get an angry mob
如果那人是我的话 我门外的草坪上
- on my front lawn.
- 早就围了一大群来算帐的人
I mean, let's be honest, Susan,
我们敞开天窗说亮话吧 Suan
You weren't exactly over the moon
当听说他们俩人要住一起的时候
- when you heard they were gonna live together.
- 你可不太高兴吧?
Well, yes, I was upset at first.
嗯 是的 我一开始的确满不是滋味的
But, you know, Mike was gonna be with someone eventually,
但是 Mike最后还是会跟别人在一起
and I consider myself lucky that it was someone, who,
我觉得这个人能是我一直以来的挚友
after all is said and done, has always been my true friend.
也是我的运气了
Susan, that's very sweet.
Susan 你这人太好了
And admirable.
令人敬佩
And abnormal.
不对劲儿
- Hey, Gaby, remember when I was with Carlos?
- 喂 Gaby 还记得我当时和Carlos在一起的时候不?
Shut it, bitch.
闭嘴 臭女人
See? That's normal.
看到没? 这才对劲儿
I'll give you $6000 for it.
我出6000美元
What? It's a $12000 oven.
什么? 这个烤箱可价值12000美元
There's a dent in the door.
在门上有个凹痕
Not a dent. A fist print.
这不是凹痕 是拳印
My husband's been a little frustrated lately.
我的丈夫最近比较烦躁
On the plus side,
顺便说下
it matches the shoe print on the dishwasher.
它和那边的洗碗机上的鞋印是一对
$6200. Take it or leave it.
6200美金 不干拉倒
Yi, yi, yi, yi.
好好好
Fine. Congratulations.
好吧 恭喜你
You just stole a pizza oven.
你刚偷到了一个比萨烤箱
Hey, Hey. I got $6200 for the oven.
嘿 那个烤箱我卖了6200美元
What?! That guy is ripping us off.
什么?! 那个家伙明摆着抢劫啊
Yeah, well, putting an "everything must go" sign,
唉 那个"一件不能剩"的标语
kind of eroded our bargaining position.
从一开始就让我们处在了被砍的局面
How are we doing on the other stuff?
那其他东西卖得怎么样?
Well, by the end of the day,
恩 在今天之前
we should be able to pay off our creditors.
我们就可以把钱都还给债主了
Give Bree back the $20000 that we owe her.
把欠Bree的20000美金还给她
And have enough to live on for...
剩下的钱还够我们用上...
45 minutes.
45分钟
Forget I asked. I don't want to talk about it now. Ohh...
就当我什么都没问 我现在什么都不想说 唉...
- Just...
- 真是...
Look, I know this is a crappy day for you.
我知道你今天过得很糟糕
But we need to start thinking,
但是我们得开始想想
- about what our plans are going to be.
- 以后的计划了
I told you, I'm gonna get a job.
我跟你说了我要找一份工作
And that is so great.
那是好事啊
- So when do you think that great thing might happen?
- 那这好事什么时候才能开始呢?
Lynette, don't.
Lynette 别逼我
- It's taken everything I got not to lose it right now.
- 我现在竭力控制情绪
Sorry.
对不起啊
You honestly think you're gonna get $200
你不会真的觉得你那个咖啡机
for that cappuccino machine?  I'll give you $50.
能卖200美金吧? 我就出50美金
- 50 bucks?! Are you...
- 50美金?! 你...
Ah, hey.
哎 喂
I think you better stop with the bargain hunting,
我觉得你最好别再砍价了
unless you want your face
除非你想让你的脸
to match the oven and the dishwasher.
和那个烤箱与洗碗机搭配成一个系列
Hey, guys!
嘿 伙计!
What the hell are they doing here?
他们来干什么?
They had theater tickets, and their sitter canceled.
他们要去看电影 他们又刚开除了保姆
- We're only gonna watch their kids for a couple hours.
- 只要照料他们的孩子几个小时就好了
Good idea, Gaby.
好主意 Gaby
We're helping the Slimeball cheat on his wife.
我们帮了Slimeball骗他的老婆
- Why not babysit for him, too?
- 为什么不再帮他带小孩呢?
Shh. Hi!
嘘 嗨!
Oh, you guys are angels for doing this.
哦 你们这么做真是好心
- Well, what are friends for?
- 要不然朋友是干嘛的呢?
speaking of which,
说到这
thanks for hooking Brad up with his new girl.
谢谢你们帮他选上新的女人
Uh, Shayla, right?
呃 Shayla 对不对?
You know, that hairstylist you recommended...
就是那个你们推荐的发型师...
Uh, I was at the mall making an appointment,
呃 我在商场见面时
and Maria walked by.
Maria正好路过
- Oh, that Shayla.
- 哦 那个Shayla
How many Shayla do you know?
你知道好几个叫Shayla的?
Two. Two.
两个 两个
There's, uh, Shayla the hairstylist
有个 呃 发型师Shayla
and then there's this other Shayla I know
还有个我认识的叫Shayla的
who's a home-wrecking whore.
是个职业妓女
Hey, Carlos. uh, why don't you take, uh, Maria and the kids
嘿 Carlos 呃 何不带Maria和孩子们
- inside and introduce them to the girls?
- 进去介绍给你女儿认识?
Come on, guys.
进去吧
- Come on in.
- 进来
All right. Let's go.
好 我们走
You're using me as an alibi now?
你利用我做证人?
I paid you 30 grand. I want my money's worth.
我付你30美元 我想物有所值
And by the way, your tennis game with Maria tomorrow...
顺便说句 你和Maria明天的网球比赛...
- you need to move it to noon.
- 需要延迟到中午
Why? So you can go get another "haircut"?
为什么? 你可以再做个"发型"?
Shayla's got a couple hours off,
Shayla刚好有几小时空闲...
- and I want to spend 'em with her.
- 我想要和她在一起
Well, Bradley, we all want things.
Bradley 我们都有想要的东西
For instance, I would like Carlos
例如 我想要Carlos
- to have a week off next month.
- 下个月有一星期的假
Impossible. It's our busiest time.
不可能 那是我们最忙的时候
Come on, Brad. We don't want to be late.
走吧 Brad 别迟到了
Oh, Gaby, we're still on for tennis tomorrow, right?
哦 Gaby 明天我们还是去打网球 对吧?
4:00?
4:00? Let me think. Uh...
4:00? 让我想下 呃...
Um...
嗯...
Actually, noon would be better for me. Could you do noon?
实际上 中午对我来说更好 中午行吗?
Oh, I was supposed to have lunch with Brad.
哦 我本应该和Brad一起吃午餐的
Do you mind, sweetie?
你介意吗 亲爱的?
Well, I was really looking forward to it,
我真的很期待和你一起吃饭
but, uh... Go ahead. You girls have fun.
但 呃... 去吧 你们玩的开心点
Listen to him. Can you believe this guy?
听听他说的 你能相信他吗?
Nope. He is not to be believed.
不能 不该相信他
My, what an interesting coat hanger.
我的天 多有趣的一个衣架啊
It's shaped like a sofa.
看起来像个沙发
Please put it in the closet.
请把它放进壁橱里
Sorry, darling.
对不起 亲爱的
Orson?
Why do you have a salt shaker from Scavo's pizzeria?
你为什么有Scavo匹萨店的盐瓶?
Oh.
哦
I stopped by to express my sympathies with Tom,
我路过向Tom表示慰问
and I... I remember looking at it,
我记得我看过它
and I... I guess I absentmindedly put it in my pocket.
我想我心不在焉地把它放进口袋了
Well, take it back now. They're liquidating,
那现在送回去 他们在清偿债务
and they're gonna need every penny they can get.
能得到的每分钱都很重要
Ma...
女士...
I want to stay here with you...
我想要留在这陪你...
Me no like the Scavos so much.
我不太喜欢Scavos那
No?
不行吗?
No.
不行
Oh. Very well.
哦 那好
- Though I'm not looking forward to going down there again.
- 虽然我很不想再去那一次
Really?
真的?
Yes. I only went down there to commiserate,
是的 我只是去那慰问的
- and he was very dismissive.
- 可他很不领情
Tom has a lot on his mind. I'm sure he didn't mean it.
Tom最近很烦 我很肯定他不是有意的
You weren't there, Bree. He was downright rude.
当时你不在那 Bree 他非常的无礼
You know, it would serve him right if I kept this.
这是给他的教训
Don't be ridiculous.
别这么荒唐了
Tom's rudeness does not give you license to steal.
Tom的无礼不是你偷东西的借口
Return it immediately.
马上就还回去
Ma, you... you such a pretty girl.
女士 像你这么漂亮的女士
I wanna live here with you. Mwah. Mwah.
我要和你住在一起 么 么
Hey.
嘿
Oh, great. You found the punch bowl.
哦 真好 你找到大酒杯了
Washed, cleaned, ready to go.
洗好了 很干净 直接就能用了
Sorry about the mess. Mike's still unpacking.
抱歉这太乱了 Mike还没开始收拾
Hey, did you manage to keep that antler chandelier out of here?
嘿 你要把那个鹿角吊灯留在这吗?
Yeah. That went right to the garage.
噢 那个丢车库了
The tough one was the framed towel
最麻烦的是那个裱起来的毛巾
with some football guy's sweat on it.
上面还有些足球运动员的汗
That "football guy" is Peyton Manning.
那个 "足球运动员" 是Peyton Manning
- You would do well to learn that name.
- 你最好记住那个名字
Ah.
啊
Oh. Wow.
哦 哇
Oh, now that I really love.
哦 我真的很喜欢它
I almost couldn't believe he had something that nice.
我都不敢相信他会有这么好的东西
- Thank you.
- 谢谢
For what?
为了什么?
I painted it. It was a gift for him.
是我画的 是送给他的礼物
Really?
真的?
You painted that. He didn't mention it.
他没说过是你画的
Yeah. It was a little beach we went to for our honeymoon.
是的 那是我们蜜月去的一个小海滩
Uh, I mean, you know how much Mike loves the ocean.
呃 我意思是 你知道 Mike很喜欢海
Yeah.
是的
Now I can see it every day.
现在我能天天看到它了
Anyway, um, can't wait for the party.
不管怎样 嗯 真希望派对马上开始
It's gonna be fun.
一定会很有趣
Yep.
是的
I'm sorry you have to go through this. It must be so hard.
要你经历这些 我很难受 那一定很艰难
The hard part was when my friend tried help me with a loan,
最难的是当我的朋友想帮我还贷款
and I thanked her by becoming a lunatic,
我却用像疯子一样
and denting her car.
砸了她的车以示感谢
Now that you brought it up,
哦 你又提这个
Lynette, I've been feeling just awful about the way
Lynette 我也很抱歉
I took over your restaurant and insulted you,
接手你的餐馆还侮辱了你
and... what can I say?
还有... 我还能说什么呢?
I think we have the kind of friendship
我想 以我们这种友情
where you don't have to say anything.
什么都不必说了
Let's just hug and move on.
让我们拥抱一下重修旧好吧
Okay?
好吗?
Oh. How's Tom holding up?
哦 Tom怎么样了?
He's doing great.
他很好
Isn't it noon?
现在不是中午了吗?
Yeah. He's up early today.
是的 他今天起得很早
He just doesn't know what he's doing next.
只是不知道接下来该做什么
Maybe I can help.
也许我能帮忙
My publisher is thinking about doing his advertising in-house,
我的出版商在考虑自己做广告
and he's been looking for someone.
他想雇个人
- Seriously?
- 真的?
Yeah.
是的
Oh, my god. That would be great.
哦 天哪 那太好了
And if he gets the job, you can actually cash the check.
如果他得到这份工作 我们就能还你钱了
I tell you what.
那么
I will invite Bruce over for dinner,
我晚上邀请Bruce来吃饭
you and Tom can join us, and we'll turn it
你和Tom也来 这样就算
- into a low pressure job interview.
- 一个轻松的面试了
Thank you. This will really cheer Tom up.
谢谢 这会让Tom高兴起来的
Great. I'll call Bruce this afternoon.
那好 下午我打电话给Bruce
Could you call him now?
你能现在打给他吗?
Hey, Mike.
嘿 Mike
Oh, I'm looking forward to one of your world-famous martinis.
哦 我一直想尝尝你出名的马提尼酒
So was Mrs. Mccluskey. She got here early.
Mccluskey夫人也是 她很早就来了
Ah. Yeah, but don't panic. I sent Edie out for more booze.
哦 是 别介意 我送给Edie的更多
Ah. So you sent the mouse to buy the cheese. Well done.
啊 让老鼠去买奶酪 做的不错
Well, look who's here.
看看这是谁
- Somebody owes me $20.
- 这下有人欠我20美元了
How about we let it ride?
再来一局吧?
Double or nothing... Mccluskey slugs someone by 5:00.
要不就赢双倍要不什么都没有... 赌Mccluskey五点到时候会打人
Katherine and I told you guys we were taking the high road.
我和Katherine说过我们处的很好
- Why won't you believe us?
- 你们为什么不相信我们?
Because I vividly remember yesterday,
因为我记得昨天
and I wasn't born during it.
我不在现场
Let me show you something I think might change your mind.
我给你们看样东西 你们就不会这么想了
So Katherine has a picture that I painted for Mike
Katherine把一幅我画给Mike的画
- hanging over her mantelpiece.
- 挂在她的壁炉前
Does she know you painted it?
她知道是你画的吗?
Yes, and we talked all about it. She loves it.
知道 我们还谈论过 她很喜欢
You painted that? Wow. You're good.
是你画的? 哇 你很厉害
- What? Where the hell is it?
- 什么? 这是什么东西?
Bye-Bye, high road.
拜拜咯 "关系很好"
What's with the puss?
这姑娘怎么了?
Katherine hung one of Mike's paintings over the mantel
Katherine挂了一副Mike的油画在壁炉架上
till she found out Susan painted it,
然后她发现是Susan画的
- then she took it down.
- 于是她把它拿下来了
Ooh. Something tells me this party's about to get good.
呵 我感觉到这个聚会渐入佳境了
You know, there could be
可能会有一个
- a perfectly innocent explanation.
- 完全不让人误会的解释
Hey, Kathy.
嘿 kathy
What happened to Susan's painting?
Susan的画怎么了?
Oh! I am such a klutz.
噢! 我真是笨手笨脚的
I was dusting yesterday,
我昨天打扫的时候
and, well, it just fell,
呃 它掉了下来
the glass shattered, and ugh.
玻璃框碎了 呃
I took it to the framer. It'll be back in a jiffy.
我就拿去装框架了 不要多久就能取回
Mm.
嗯
Oh! Excuse me.
噢! 请原谅
See, a perfectly innocent...
听见了吗 完全不会令人误解的...
bald-faced lie.
睁眼瞎话
It is possible.
这是有可能的
I just drained a pitcher of martinis.
我只喝了一壶马提尼酒
I'm not buying it.
我不会信的
Really, Susan, there's not a woman in the world
真的 Susan 世界上没有女人
- who doesn't know what "I broke it dusting" means.
- 不知道"我打扫时打破的"真正含义
That's how I got rid
这也是我为什么
of Tom's last bottle of "musk, the cologne for men."
不相信Tom说的最后一瓶是"男人的古龙水"
All right, you guys think what you want.
好吧 随你们怎么想
I'm gonna choose to believe her.
我相信她
All right, so we have whiskey and bourbon.
好了 已经有威士忌和波旁威士忌了
What else does Mike want?
Mike还要些什么?
Bup, bup, bup. We need a system.
我们得有条理些
Let's start over there in Scotland,
先从Scotland区开始
hand over to Russia and walk our way around the globe.
然后去Russia区 绕地球一周
- Wow. It's crowded in here.
- 哇 这儿真拥挤
They're all buying lottery tickets.
他们都是来买彩票的
The jackpot's $100 million.
累积奖金有一亿美元
Look. there's a priest.
瞧 那儿有位神父
I knew that vow of poverty was a crock.
我就知道贫穷誓言(神职人员对保持清贫的誓言)都是骗人的
Hello!
你好!
You remember me?
还记得我吗?
Father Drance.
我是Drance神父
I... I didn't know you'd moved back to the area.
我不知道你已经搬回来了
oh, I just remembered. Mike wants vermouth.
噢 我刚想起 Mike要苦艾酒
Can you grab that before we forget?
在我们没忘记之前你能去拿吗?
Sure.
当然
Right away.
立刻就去
It's wonderful to see you looking so well. I...
你看上去很好 真是太好了 我...
Shut up.
闭嘴
I'm only gonna say this once. I've moved on.
我只说一次 我已经摆脱过去了
I've remarried, I have a new life,
我结婚了 也有了全新的生活
and it's the way I want it to stay... new.
这就是我想要保留住的... 崭新的一切
Of course.
当然
So, uh, what was that about?
这是怎么一回事?
Oh. He said we sat together once on a airplane.
噢 他说我们曾在飞机上坐一起
Apparently he's less memorable than he thinks he is.
显然他没自己想的那么值得记忆
Come on. I don't want to miss the party.
走吧 我不想错过了聚会
Fine.
好的
Fine. I will do it, but you owe me.
好的 我会去做的 但你欠我一次
I gotta go.
我得挂了
Let me guess. Brad.
让我猜看看 是Brad
- Yes, he wants me to take Maria shopping tomorrow.
- 是的 他想让我明天约上Maria去购物
Yeah, so he can grab a quickie.
所以他就能快活一把
You know, this whole thing is disgusting.
你知道吗 这整件事真让人厌恶
- I can't take it anymore.
- 我不想再这样了
I know. Just keep reminding yourself
我知道 但你得记住
that we're geting things out of it, too.
我们也从中得到了一些东西
Things I don't want. Things I haven't earned.
那些我不是想要的 那些不是我劳动所得的
No, I'm gonna tell Bradley we're out.
不行 我得去告诉Bradley我们不做了
What? you can't do that.
什么? 你不能这样做
- You'll lose your job and all that money.
- 你会丢了工作和那一大笔钱的
I don't care about the money.
我不在乎这钱
I do...
我在乎...
and so does my personal shopper and pilates instructor.
还有我的私人导购和瑜珈教练也在乎
Gaby, no. We're doing the right thing.
Gaby 不 我们该做正确的事
Or we can...
或者我们可以...
make someone else do the right thing.
让别人做对的事
Gaby, what does that mean?
Gaby 你是什么意思?
It means...
意思是...
tomorrow I'm going to the mall
明天我会去购物中心
to get my hair cut by a slut.
让一个荡妇帮我理发
Hey. Uh, look at what I found... my beach painting.
嘿 看我找到了什么... 我的海滩作品
Oh, yeah. Katherine told me it broke.
噢 是的 Katherine告诉我它摔坏了
Sorry about that.
很抱歉
Yeah, that's what she told me, too,
是的 她也是这么跟我说的
only, uh, it didn't.
只是 它没坏
That's weird. Why would she...
这真奇怪 她为什么...
I don't know.
我不知道
She seemed to love the painting...
她看上去很喜欢这幅作品...
until I told her that I painted it.
直到我告诉她这是我画的
Excuse me just a minute.
等我一下
I'm not making a big deal.
我没说这是大不了的事情
- I just want to know why you lied.
- 我只想知道你为什么说谎
Mike, please, not now.
Mike 拜托 现在不是时候
- We have a house full of guests.
- 我们有一屋子的客人
No, we'll talk about this now.
不 我们现在就谈论这个
- What are you doing?
- 你在干什么?
Uh, nothing.
呃 没事
Susan showed me the painting.
Susan给我看了那副画
- There's not a scratch on it.
- 那上面根本没有刮痕
She what?!
她什么?
You did it.
你做的
Susan!
susan!
- I hope you enjoyed that.
- 希望你乐在其中
I didn't.
并没有
I didn't. Uh...
我没有 嗯...
So what are we thinking?
想修什么样的发型?
Well, Shayla... It is Shayla, right?
Shayla... 你是叫shayla 对吧?
Mm-hmm.
嗯... 嗯
- I need a fresh look.
- 我需要一个全新的造型
Mm.
嗯
I've been going through
我最近有
some pretty intense pepersonal stuff lately.
一段相当刺激的经历
Oh. Really?
噢 是吗?
Fine. I'll tell you.
好吧 我告诉你
I have been having an affair with a married man,
我有了外遇 是和一个已婚男人
and it's come to that point
然后看着镜子时
where I can't even look at myself in the mirror.
我无颜面对自己
So I want a new style that says I'm not a giant turd of sin.
所以我想换个新造型 表明我不是那种罪恶深重的人
Well, it's not your fault
爱上一个已婚男人
- that you fell in love with a married man.
- 并不是你的过错
Yeah, that's what I thought at first,
是的 当初我也是这么认为的
and then I realized that's stupid.
可我意识到这种想法很愚蠢
I mean, what about his poor wife?
我的意思是 他可怜的太太怎么办?
Well, maybe she doesn't love him enough.
可能她不够爱他
Oh, no. she does. She loves him plenty.
不 不 她爱她的丈夫 深爱着
So you want to take the bangs up a little bit?
你要刘海蓬一点吗?
And he has kids... two adorable little kids.
而且他有小孩了... 两个天真可爱的孩子
That's sad,
真遗憾
but sometimes you just have to look out for yourself.
但有时你得为自己想想
Well, maybe I am tired of being that kind of selfish bitch.
可能我厌倦了做那种自私自利的婊子
Have you ever considered, uh, highlights?
你有考虑过挑染吗?
Focus, Shayla! We are talking about
专心点 Shayla! 我们在谈论
how I'm ruining innocent people's lives.
我如何毁了无辜人的生活
Gaby, you seem like a lovely, warm person.
Gaby 你看起来是一个温暖可爱的人
Stop beating yourself up.
不要再折腾自己了
Oh, for god sakes, you bleached blonde twit.
噢 老天 你这个金发碧眼的笨蛋
I'm not talking about me. I'm talking about you and Bradley.
我说的不是我 我说的是你和Bradley
What? What... what is this? Who... who are you?
什么? 这是... 这是怎么一回事? 你... 你是谁?
I'm a friend of Maria's, who, by the way,
我是Maria的朋友 随便提一下
happens to be a warm and lovely person.
她刚好是一个温暖可爱的人
Well, maybe she is, but Brad doesn't love her.
或许她是 但Brad并不爱她
He says he's gonna leave her.
他说了会离开她的
Oh, Shayla, he's lying. She's pregnant.
噢 Shayla 他在说谎 他太太怀孕了
That's impossible. They haven't had sex in over a year.
那不可能 他们已经一年多时间没有性生活了
Well, call the vatican,
打电话给罗马教廷说
"Cause we're gonna need a manger and some hay."
"这是因为我们需要一个食槽和一些干草"
- Get out.
- 出去
I'm just trying to protect you here.
我在尝试着保护你
I said get out now.
我说了 现在出去
Okay, let's just take a deep breath here...
好吧 深呼吸...
Let's not do anything we're gonna regret.
别做一些会让我们后悔的事情来
Now.
立刻
This is why people should never get their hair cut in a mall!
这就是为什么人们不应该来购物中心剪头发!
Ohh. you couldn't shave?
噢 你不能刮下胡子吗?
Come on, Tom. You need to look nice.
拜托 Tom 你得看上去精神奕奕
Bree's going to a lot of trouble for this dinner.
否则整顿饭会给Bree添不少麻烦的
What, is she debuting a new salmon puff?
怎么了 她试做新的鲑鱼松饼了?
Okay. I was going to wait
好吧 我本来想等到你
to tell you this when you were in a good mood,
心情好些的时候再谈
but I realize that's not gonna happen,
可我意识到了这不可能
so Bree has a special guest tonight, her publisher...
Bree今晚有个特别的客人 她的出版商...
and as luck would have it,
嗯 碰巧
he's looking to hire a new marketing executive.
他正在招市场主管
Oh, my god. What are you...
噢 天呐 你在...
are you tricking me into a job interview?
你是在设计我去一个工作面试么?
I'll find something, okay? I just need some time.
我会找到的 行不行? 我只是需要点时间
you're grieving. I get it.
你很难受 我知道
But this sounds like a fantastic job.
可这像是个很棒的工作
Please just hear the guy out and make a nice...
就只是听完他说的...
Impression.
留下个好印象
Fine. I'll shave.
得了 我去刮胡子
And brush your teeth. My eyes are watering.
还要刷牙 我眼眶都湿了
Oh.
哦
and don't just wet the toothbrush.
牙刷别敷衍了事
I can tell.
我看得出来
Bruce. Hello.
Bruce 你好
Hi. come on in. Hi.
嗨 进来吧 你好
Hi. Thank you so much for joining us tonight.
嗨 十分感谢你今晚到我们这儿来
May I take your coat?
我能帮你挂外套么?
Sure. Let me.
当然 让我来
Oh, wait. Let me get my "brain" out of there.
哦 等一下 让我把我的"智囊" 拿出来
I never go anywhere without this.
没有它我哪儿也不去
That way, when I get a bright idea...
这样 当我有灵感的时候...
Wham! Right into the tape recorder.
哇噢! 立马存到录音笔里
Huh. Sounds like quite a handy gizmo. Thank you, Orville.
哈 像是个很方便的小发明 谢谢 Orville
It's Orson...
他叫Orson...
Orville, Orson... Either way, he came home from the playground
Orville Orson... 哪个都一样 他总是鼻青脸肿地
covered in bruises. Am I right?
从操场回家 我说中了吗?
Idea for children's book...
关于儿童书籍的想法...
Kid who gets the crap kicked out of him
有个蠢名字的小孩子
cause he has a goofy name. Could be "Orson."
会被打得屁滚尿流 可以叫 "Orson"
Oh, that's them. Wait till you meet Tom.
哦 他们来了 等你见到Tom
You'll be so glad you had that tape recorder.
你会很庆幸带了录音笔
He's just bursting with ideas.
他就是思如泉涌
Hi. Lynette, Tom, hi.
嗨 Lynette Tom 嗨
Hey. I'd like you to meet my publisher, Bruce.
嘿 我来向你们引见我的出版商 Bruce
It's nice to meet you.
见到你很高兴
Hey. Bree, I'm getting a beer, if you don't mind.
嘿 Bree 我向来杯啤酒 如果你不介意的话
Hey, Katherine.
嘿 Katherine
Mike is standing across the street
Mike就站在对面看着
watching to make sure I apologize,
确保我道歉了
even though it's clear to me you're the one who should
尽管对我来说你才是该
be apologizing for the way you ruined my party.
为破坏我的宴会而道歉的人
One, two, three.
一 二 三
Well, that should be long enough, so here.
好了 应该够长了 那么
Kiss my ass. Bye.
去你的吧 再见
Hold on.
等一等
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
But neither of us exactly gets a gold star for model behavior.
可我们俩谁都不可能得最佳表现奖
It's not the same.
那不是一回事儿
Why not? I mean, you loved that painting
怎么不是? 我意思是 你很喜欢那幅画
until you found out that I did it,
直到你发现是我画的
and then you acted totally petty.
然后你就变得十分小气
So why am I the only bad guy here?
为什么站这儿的只有我是坏人?
Let me ask you something, okay?
让我问你点事儿 行吧?
Didn't it give you just the tiniest little thrill
难道告诉我那幅我是如此喜爱的画儿
to tell me that
是你画的 还有我房子里放着些
that painting that I was so happy about was yours?
代表你跟Mike之间爱情的东西
That I had something in my house
就没有让你感到
that represented the love between you and Mike?
哪怕是一丁点儿的兴奋吗?
No.
没有
Then what are you doing, Susan?
那你这么做是什么意思 Susan?
Can't you see how hard this is for me?
你就看不出来这对我有多难么?
You live right across the street.
你就在正对面住着
You guys share a kid.
你们俩有个孩子
Do I have to have a painting of your honeymoon, too?
我是不是还得留着你们蜜月时的画儿?
Look, I knew I wasn't going to get
听着 我知道我不可能
a clean slate with Mike, okay?
跟Mike从新来过 懂不懂?
I just wanted a clean mantelpiece.
我只是想要个新的壁炉台
Fantastic dinner, Bree. This was a great idea.
晚餐棒极了 Bree 这主意真不错
Well, I just wanted to get you together with Tom here.
还凑合 我只是想让你跟Tom在这儿聚聚
I thought you two might hit it off.
我想你们合得来
Yeah. Tom, Bree says you used to be quite the ad wiz.
对了 Tom Bree说你可是个广告奇才
Oh, I don't know.
哦 我不知道
He's being modest. He was the best.
他谦虚了 他是最棒的
Good, because I'm looking
那就好 我正在找一个
for someone to head up a new division.
新部门的领头人
I'm going to put some coffee on.
我去准备些咖啡
Orson, would you give me a hand?
Orson 能来给我帮个忙吗?
Let these three chat.
让他们仨好好聊聊
So do you think you have any interest
那么你有兴趣做回
in getting back in the game?
以前的工作吗?
I don't know.
我不知道
the timing's a little weird.
时机有点怪
How so?
怎么会?
I don't know.
我不知道
Well, Tom was just running a very successful restaurant,
是这样 Tom之前在经营一家很成功的饭店
and he just sold it at a handsome profit.
他刚转手赚了一大笔
So he's waiting for the right opportunity.
所以他在等好机会
You might have to do a little selling here, Bruce.
Bruce 你是不是也介绍下你的公司?
Huh. I guess the good ones are always the hardest to land.
啊哈 我想越是好的越难敲定
Yeah.
是啊
Let me give it a shot.
我来说说
We represent a small stable
我们代表的是全球一小部分
of elite nonfiction authors from all over the world.
精英纪实文学作家
So you'd be working closely with those writers
所以你将会跟这些作家一起工作
to come up with creative approaches to selling their books.
为他们作品销售出注意
That sounds... Amazing...
那听起来... 难以置信...
I don't know.
我不知道
Are there more potatoes?
还有土豆吗?
You can have mine.
你可以吃我的
Stop saying, "I don't know."
别再说 "我不知道"了
Hmm.
呃
Sounds like there's a lot of traveling.
听起来要经常出差
I'm not, you know, really big on living out of a suitcase.
我不是 你知道的 太喜欢旅行箱生活
Even to do two weeks at the book fair in Paris
就连呆在Paris的五星级酒店里
while you stay at a five-star hotel?
做两周的书展也不例外?
Paris?
巴黎?
Like France?
法国?
Yes, like the greatest city in the world.
对 就像在世界上最好的城市
Gee, I'm getting Lynette excited.
哇噢 我倒是让Lynette激动了
Too bad you don't have any advertising experience.
你没有任何广告的经验真是太糟了
Oh.
哦
Actually, I have 12 years of experience.
事实上我有12年的工作经验
Really?
真的吗?
Yeah.
真的
I was account executive for eight years,
我做过八年的财务主管
V.P. for four more after that,
之后又做了四年副总裁
and by the way, I wrote my graduate thesis
顺便提一下 我毕业论文是关于
on the rise of the nonfiction novel.
非小说类文学作品的发展
Wow.
哇哦
I know. So what kind of starting salary are we talking about?
我知道 那么我们所谈的起薪有多少?
Lynette, can I see you for a sec?
Lynette 能单独谈会儿吗?
Okay. Bruce, could you hold that thought?
好的 Bruce 你能先保留那个想法吗?
I'm gonna be right back.
我马上就回来
Well, we're on pins and needles.
嗯 我们正如坐针毡呢
How's it going?
怎么样?
What the hell are you doing? I'm getting this job. That's what I'm doing.
你他妈的在干嘛? 我在争取这份工作 这就是我在做的
I thought it was my job. Well, you're not acting like you want it very much, mister...
我认为这是我的工作 那么你表现的并不像你很想要...
"uh, I don't know.
"我不知道 还有土豆吗?"先生
are there any more potatoes?" It's not that I don't want it.
我不是不想要
It's just that it's all happening so fast.
只是这一切发生的太快了
I need a little time to lick my wounds.
我需要点时间来重整旗鼓
Okay, you lick. I'm going to Paris.
那好 你修整吧 我要去巴黎了
You're not taking my job.
你不能抢走我的工作
Your job? The one you're magically gonna get by sulking
你的工作? 你经常莫名其妙地生闷气
and acting like a brat? You had a shot. You blew it.
孩子般的对待工作? 你是有机会 但你却搞砸了
- Oh, yeah?
- 是吗?
Yeah.
是
You just messed with the bull, sister,
你这是惹火上身
prepare to get the horns.
自取其辱
I...
我...
Maybe we should slice the tart in here,
或许我们应该在这里把馅饼切好
I don't want to bring a large knife into this.
我可不想把刀带进去
Bruce...
I was just saying to Lynette,
我刚和Lynette谈了
I gave you my, I don't really care about this job thing
我放弃  我真的不在乎这个工作
to see if you really care about this job,
只想看看你是否在乎这个工作
and you do, and I like that.
你很在乎 我很高兴
Clever.
明智之举
Now we haven't talked compensation package yet,
现在我们还没有谈补偿事宜
but I got a good feeling...
但是我有个好的预感...
You know, Tom, you're right. Bruce does care about this job,
你知道 Tom 你是对的 Bruce确实很在意这个工作
that's why he wants to make sure
这就是他想确认
he gets the perfect person for it.
他找到了最合适的人选
Well, Lynette, you yourself said I was the best.
嗯 Lynette 你自己说过我是最好的
Oh, you were. You were the best person who ever worked for me.
哦 你是 你曾是我最好的员工
I used to be his boss.
我曾是他的老板
- This is not what I had in mind.
- 这不是我想的那样
I don't know
我不明白
why either one of them wants to work for that jackass.
为什么他们俩都想为那个混蛋工作
Now, now, he's been very good to me.
不 不 他对我很好
Well, of course he has,
是的 他是得对你好
because he knows you make him a lot of money.
因为他知道你给他赚了很多钱
Me, on the other hand, he sees as an insignificant little man,
我 从另一方面来说 在他眼里我是个微不足道的家伙
barely worth mentioning
不值一提
as he talks into his annoying, penis-shaped tape recorder.
像他在那个讨厌的像鸡巴的录音笔里说的
So I said to him,
接着我对他说
"je crois que c'est l'homme qui fait les chez d'oeuvres."
"我认为是人在做工作"
and he said to me, "non, lynette.
然后他对我说 "不 Lynette.
ce sont les chez d'oeuvres qui font l'homme."
是工作在做人"
Great story... I assume.
我想这是个精彩的故事...
I don't speak another language, but I've had ad campaigns
我不说其他外语 但是我曾有个广告活动
translated into 12 different ones,
翻译成了12种外语
including Professor Crispy's potato chips.
包括Professor Crispy牌薯条
I love that campaign. You did that?
我喜欢哪个活动 是你做的?
I did.
是的
Yes. Tom was very good at his job,
是的 Tom在被炒鱿鱼之前
right up until he got fired.
是个好职员
Well, actually, I was relieved to get fired.
嗯 其实 被炒鱿鱼我倒是松了口气
My boss was kind of a ball-buster.
我的老板是个刻薄鬼
Oops. She's right here.
哦 她就在这儿
Je regrette.
我很遗憾
Oh, would anyone care for something sweet?
哦 有人想吃点甜品嘛?
I know I would.
我想来点
Well, we've all had our troubles as bosses, haven't we, Tom?
嗯 我们自己做老板的时候总是有些棘手的事情 是不是 Tom?
I was sort of sugarcoating it
当我说餐馆经营的很成功的时候
when I said his restaurant was very successful.
有点言过其实了
The truth is, he mismanaged that pizza joint
事实是 那个披萨餐馆
right into the ground.
他经营不善
Let me be very clear.
让我明说吧
I think Lynette is fantastic.
我觉得Lynette很出色
She is a great manager.
是个很优秀的管理者
She's got terrific people skills
有纯熟的交际技巧
and is very reliable...
而且十分可靠...
As long as the cancer doesn't flare up again,
只要癌症不再发作
You know what?
你知道吗?
It's getting late.
天色晚了
I should probably hit the road.
我得走了
But what about the job?
那工作的事情怎么办啊?
Yeah...
嗯...
I just started looking. I'm sure it's gonna be a long process,
我才开始招聘 我想这还需要一段时间
but trust me, you've certainly made an impression.
但是相信我 你们给我留下了深刻的印象
I'll get your coat.
我去给你拿外衣
Oh, it's a shame you can't stay for dessert.
哦 真遗憾 你不留下来吃点甜点
I've made tarte tatin.
我做了苹果挞
Idea for novel...
小说构想
Woman who's married to a gay man and doesn't know it.
一个女人和一个同性恋男人结婚了还浑然不知
Well, thanks again.
嗯 再次感谢
I don't know when I've had such an interesting evening.
我不记得什么时候还能有这么一个难忘的夜晚
I'll call you tomorrow. We'll talk about your friends.
明天给你电话 到时我们再谈你朋友的事情
Uh, Bruce,
呃 Bruce
- Why don't I wrap up a piece of that tart to go.
- 我给你包一份苹果挞回去如何?
Yeah.
好的
Give it.
给他
- Give what?
- 给什么?
Bruce's tape recorder.
Bruce的录音器啊
- I don't know what...
- 我不知道什么...
you took it. I saw you.
你明明拿了 我看你拿的
Hey, has anybody seen my tape recorder?
嘿 有没有谁看到我的录音器?
- It was right here.
- 本来放在这的
I'll look.
我来找找看
Hey.
嘿
Ah.
啊
Stop.
住手
- I don't have it. Ooh!
- 我没拿 噢!
What do you call this?
那你说这是什么
Uh, Bruce is looking for, uh...
呃 Bruce在找 呃
Never mind.
没事了
We will talk about this later.
等会我再和你算这帐
Look what we got brought in the dirty napkins.
看看我们在餐巾纸里找到什么了
Thanks.
谢谢
- Hello, Gaby.
- 你好 Gaby
Ooh!
啊!
Jeez, Bradley, you scared me!
我的天 Bradley 你吓到我了!
- You talked to Shayla.
- 你和Shayla说了是吧
Yeah, she's a real gem.
是的 她可是个难得的好女人
You shouldn't have done that. We have a deal.
你怎么可以这么做 我们说好了的
Well, I'm tired of the deal,
好啦 我倦透了这鬼交易
and what you're doing to Maria is despicable.
你对Maria的所作所为真是太可鄙了
Hey, you're in no position to judge me,
嘿 你没资格评论我
don't forget, I was working with Carlos when you cheated on him.
别忘了 我和Carlos做同事那会你还对他不忠
Yeah, well, I'm not that person anymore.
是啊 呃 我早就迷途知返了
I've changed.
我已经变了
Right, you're worse.
没错你是变了 变得更可恶
You're so worried about Maria,
你一缺钱或是假期要没了
until there's money or vacation time at stake,
你就开始关心Maria了
then you're only worried about Gaby.
完了你就只关心你自己
You know what you're right.
听着 你全说对了
I'm out.
我不干了
- What do you mean?
- 你不干了是什么意思?
Deal's over.
交易结束
I'm not covering for your stupid little fling anymore.
我再也不要帮你隐瞒你那可笑的风流韵事
It's not a fling. I love her.
那不是风流韵事 我爱她
She's the most incredible woman I've ever met.
她是我见过最值得信赖的女人
Shayla? She is a Hello Kitty tip jar.
Shayla? 她说话没点脑子
Well, she makes me happy. I can't give her up.
但是 和她在一起我很快乐 我没法抛弃她
Well, at least be man enough to tell Maria.
但是 你至少应该诚实点告诉Maria
Because if you don't, I will.
因为你不说 我就会替你说
All right, fine.
好了 好极了
I will tell Maria.
我会告诉Maria的
And you can tell Carlos
而你就可以告诉Carlos
to bring a box to work on Monday, 'cause he's fired.
星期一带个盒子来 因为他被炒了
So dinner...
这样的晚餐可真是
Wow.
好极了
Lynette, I will regret for the rest of my life
Lynette 我一辈子都会为此而歉疚的
What I said tonight.
我说的那些话
I... I don't know what's going on with me.
我... 我不知道我是怎么了
I don't do, and it's okay.
我明白 也没关系
Besides, did you hear what came out of my mouth,
除了那些 你听到我嘴里蹦出来的什么话吧
like I said... wow.
像我说的那样... 好极了
Wouldn't you love to hear what Bruce said
Bruce开车回去的时候
into his tape recorder on the ride home
对着他的录音器说的话那才有趣呢
Idea...  Check local mental hospital
构想... 检查当地的精神病院
for escaped married couple.
是否有逃跑的已婚夫妇
So...
那么...
Were you serious about wanting to go back to work?
你是真的想工作吗
I was talking about that job tonight.
今晚我一直在喋喋不休的讲那份工作的事情
And trying to convince Bruce I was good,
想让Bruce相信我很优秀
And I remembered something. I am good.
我想到了以前 我本来就很优秀
And I would like another chance to prove it.
我想要其他的机会证明我自己
Okay.
好吧
Really?
真的?
Yeah. We did my thing for seven years.
当然 我做自己喜欢的事已经7年了
Now it's your turn.
现在该你了
Oh!
哦!
Do you know how embarrassed I would have been
你知道吗 如果Bruce看到你拿的
if Bruce had seen you take it?
我有多难堪?
He deserved it. He insulted me.
他活该 他侮辱过我
So say something. Stand up to him. But stealing?
那就有话直说 当面讲清楚 为什么要偷东西呢?
Honestly, Orson, why would you do something like that?
老实说 Orson 你为什么要那么做?
I don't know, Bree.
我也不知道 Bree
I don't. Here's something I do know...
我不知道 不过有一点我知道...
When I was a successful dentist,
过去我是一个杰出的牙科医生的时候
No one spoke to me the way they do now.
没人像现在这么对我说话
When I lost my practice, I lost people's respect.
我失去了工作 也失去了人们对我的尊敬
And you hope to earn it back through larceny?
那么你想通过偷窃挽回面子?
You haven't walked in my shoes.
你没到我这地步
Tom lost his job. Everyone jumped to his rescue.
Tom丢了工作 所有人去帮助他
Even you...
甚至你...
Bending over backwards trying to get him a job.
也拼命帮他找工作
I don't need to walk in your shoes, Orson.
我没必要为你着想 Orson
What you did was embarrassing and childish,
你的行为让人难堪 而且很幼稚
And it's never gonna happen again.
希望以后永远别再发生
Understood?
知道了吗?
See you. Thank you.
再见 谢谢
- Father?
- 神父?
Yes. Can I help you?
哦 有什么事能帮你吗?
Oh, I hope so. I, uh, saw you the other night
哦 是的 呃 前几天晚上我看到你
when you were buying your lottery ticket.
你当时正在买彩票
I was with my husband Dave.
我和老公Dave在一起
Ah.
啊
Yes. He said that you barely know each other,
对 他说你们不认识彼此
But it didn't seem that way to me.
但是我觉得不是这样
And, well,
还有
He refuses to talk about his past,
他拒绝谈论他的过去
So if there is anything that you could tell me about him...
那么你能不能告诉我 一点关于他的事情...
I'm not sure I can do that.
我觉得我不能
Please. He has so many secrets,
求求你 他有太多秘密
And I don't have anyone else to turn to.
我又找不到 其他可求助的人
I wish I could help you, but...
我也想帮你 但是...
This is something you need to discuss with your husband.
这是你们夫妻之间的事
Well, if it was that easy,
哎呀 如果真有那么容易
- Do you think that I would be here?
- 我还会来找您吗?
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
Please know that my thoughts are with you both, Mrs. Dash.
我一直挂念着你们俩 Dash夫人
It's Williams.
是Williams夫人
I'm too old-school for my own good.
我虽有些保守 但是是为你自己好
I shouldn't just assume that you took your husband's name.
我不应该简单地认为 你用你老公的姓
Anyway...
无论如何...
Good luck, Mrs. Williams.
祝你好运 Williams夫人
Hey, Susan. I thought I had M.J. till 7.
嘿 Susan 我想我该7点去接M.J.
Uh, you do. I am here to take my painting back.
哦 我知道 我来取走我的画
But you gave it to me. It's mine.
但是你已经给我了 它是我的
Well, now I'm ungiving it. Try to keep up.
哦 我现在又不想给你了 我要自己收藏
Okay, if this is about what happened at the housewarming...
嗯 如果你是为乔迁庆宴上的事情...
It is, actually,
是的 确实是
because that is when I decided
因为就在那个时候 我决定
that I don't want this piece of art that I slaved over
我不想要这幅我辛辛苦苦挂上去
hanging in the house you are sharing
而你却和你的新女朋友
with your new girlfriend. Capisce?
一起住在房子里 明白吗?
Okay, so the other night you were mad
好啊 前几天晚上你还怪我
because it wasn't hanging up, but now you want to take it?
我没把它挂起来 但是现在你又想拿走它?
Yep. I'm complicated like that. Aren't you glad you divorced me?
没错 我就是这么麻烦 要不你怎么会和我离婚?
If you two want a painting so bad, paint your own.
如果你俩这么想要这幅画 你们自己画去
- Susan...
Mayfair.
Mayfair
Stay out of this.
别掺乎
This is between me and my ex.
这是我和我前夫之间的事
Got it?
明白吗?
Unbelievable.
不可理喻
Anyway, I'm thinking a brighter color for the baby's room.
总之 我在想婴儿房涂成明亮的颜色
Now I know it's a bit of a stretch,
现在我觉得还得考虑考虑
but how do you feel about turquoise?
你觉得宝石绿怎么样?
Sweetheart?
亲爱的?
We need to talk.
我想和你谈谈
What you reading?
你在看什么?
The want ads.
招聘信息
Can't decide if I should be a data entry operator
我不能决定是做一个数据录入员呢
or join the marines.
还是参加海军
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉
Don't be. I told you, I hated working for that jackass.
不用 我跟你说过 我讨厌为那个混蛋打工
- You did the right thing.
- 你做的对
I should have done it sooner.
我早该那么做了
But you did it,
但是你已经做了
Even though you knew you were gonna lose a lot of money.
尽管你知道 你会少赚很多钱
You're a good person, babe. I'm very proud of you.
你是好人 宝贝儿 我为你骄傲
Well, that means a lot, coming from a united states marine.
哦 那意义重大 若你从海军退役回来
Mm.
嗯
Hello?
你好?
Maria.
Maria
Calm down.
冷静
Okay, we're coming over.
好吧 我们这就过去
I guess Bradley told her.
我猜Bradley告诉她了
Thanks for coming.
谢谢你们过来
I didn't know who else to call.
我不知道还能打电话给谁
It was horrible.
太可恶了
He just kept telling me he loves her.
他不停地说他爱她
She's the best thing that ever happened to him.
她是他今生的真爱
He finally understands what love means.
他终于明白了爱的真谛
I just wanted him to stop talking.
我只想让他住嘴
You should never be too impressed
有礼貌的人总是
by people with good manners.
给人留下深刻印象
They're the ones who will give a friendly wave
即使他们偷走了你的东西
even when they've stolen from you...
他们还向你友好地挥手...
They're the type to sweetly welcome you...
即使他想揭穿你的隐私...
even as they try to uncover your secrets...
他们仍然甜美地欢迎你...
They're the kind to offer you coffee,
即使他们要将你报警
even as they report you to the police.
他们还会给你端来咖啡
And don't be too offended by someone who's openly rude...
不要冲那些貌似粗鲁的人发火...
Because they may be that way
因为那可能是他们
for the nicest of reasons.
表达好意的方式